<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Alchemist Simulator on Documentation for the Alchemist Simulator</title>
    <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Alchemist Simulator on Documentation for the Alchemist Simulator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:24:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:24:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Tutorials are lessons that take the reader by the hand through a series of steps. They are meant to show a beginner that they can achieve something with Alchemist.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How-to Guides</title>
      <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/howtos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/howtos/</guid>
      <description>How-to guides take the reader through the steps required to solve a real-world problem. They are recipes, directions to achieve a specific end: while a tutorial is what a beginner needs to know, a how-to guide is an answer to a question that only a user with some experience could even formulate. In how-to guides, we assume some knowledge and understanding, we assume that the user already knows how to do basic things and use basic tools.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation</title>
      <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/explanation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/explanation/</guid>
      <description>Explanation, or discussions, clarify and illuminate a particular topic. They are a chance for the documentation to relax and step back from the software, taking a wider view, illuminating it from a higher level or even from different perspectives. You might imagine a discussion document being read at leisure, rather than over the code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference</title>
      <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/reference/</guid>
      <description>Reference guides are technical, austere, and to the point descriptions of the machinery and how to operate it. Reference guides have one job only: to describe. They are code-determined, because ultimately that’s what they describe: key classes, functions, APIs, and so they list things like functions, fields, attributes and methods, and set out how to use them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/license/</guid>
      <description>Legal information The Alchemist Simulator License Explanation for humans Alchemist adopts a GNU GPLv3 license with a permissive modification. Alchemist or parts of it can be used in commercial products and closed-source software components, as far as they are not mutated. Namely, the GPLv3 is extended with a linking/classpath exception, so it can be used freely as a library, but modified versions the software must instead be released with a GPLv3 compatible lincesing scheme.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alchemistsimulator.github.io/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Examples from published papers Showcase Contents 2020: Optimal resilient distributed data collection in mobile edge environments Simulation of crowd control with mobile in Turin.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>